https://goodluckrice.com/index.php?main_page=privacy&zenid=0a5312e3b2409c19e29f3d0792da114d

Privacy Notice
Our Commitment To Privacy :Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. We track IP Addresses:Your IP address is used to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer the Web site, in addition your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. The Information We Collect:This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the goodluckrice.com website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: Name, Address, Email address, Phone number, Credit/Debit Card Information, (etc.) On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are: Name, Address, Phone Number, (etc.) The Way We Use Information:We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. We offer gift-cards by which you can personalize a product you order for another person. Information you provide to us to create a gift-card is only used for that purpose, and it is only disclosed to the person receiving the gift. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. You can register with our website if you would like to receive our catalog as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. Our Commitment To Data Security:To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We take credit card information security seriously and use a variety of technical solutions to make shopping safe at our Site. Furthermore, your information is encrypted and is protected utilizing the industry standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption software. SSL encrypts all of your personal information, including your credit card number, your name, and your address, so that the information cannot be read as it travels over the Internet. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. If at any point you do not feel comfortable ordering on the web or simply need more product information please call one of our helpful telephone reps or simply send us an email sales@goodluckrice.com This site provides the choice to Opt In or Out:Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor. This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. Each time an information email is distributed, you have the option to use unique unsubscribe url which is attached to each outgoing email. Customers may unsubscribe at any time by simply logging into their accounts. Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by simply visit the customer login area of this website. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. How To Contact Us:Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 407-340-7007 or send us an email at sales@goodluckrice.com.
Information
Shipping & Returns
Privacy Notice
Conditions of Use
Contact Us
Newsletter Unsubscribe
Reviews  [more]
Eric; I really love the keyring I ordered. I'm sure my daugh ..
Home
::
Privacy Notice
::
Shipping & Returns
::
Conditions of Use
::
Contact Us
Your IP Address is:
72.182.10.230
Copyright © 2020 www.goodluckrice.com
